sitesondisplay.com 2017-08-07

# SitesOnDisplay.com : Privacy Statement

## Privacy Statement

### Privacy Policy Overview

This Privacy Policy covers the SitesOnDisplay treatment of personal information that is recorded when you submit your site for inclusion in our database.

Our privacy policy does not apply to the practices of other companies advertised, or otherwise listed, on the SitesOnDisplay web site, nor does it extend to people that SitesOnDisplay does not employ or manage.

### Information Collection and Use

SitesOnDisplay offers free Standard site listings and paid inclusion Featured Listings. The information we collect is dependent on your needs.

For Standard Site submissions, the only information collected is Name, Email Address, and URL. Additional information is collected for Featured Site listings, but these can only be purchased at ExactSeek.com.

Your use of SitesOnDisplay's services constitutes a business relationship wherein we provide a promotion service for your web site(s). In exchange, SitesOnDisplay reserves the right to use the contact information collected during site submission to deliver notices regarding changes or updates to our service, to provide free newsletters (SiteProNews and SEO-News), to inform you of additions to the Jayde Online Network of web sites, or to send announcements and carefully screened offers and information on behalf of our partners or advertisers.

With the exception of auto-response messages which are sent at the time of site submission and which contain important confirmation details regarding your site listing, you may remove yourself from any or all other notice and announcement mailings at anytime using the unsubscribe methods provided in those mailings. Any mailing received from our company is clearly identified and includes at least 2 methods to remove yourself from future mailings. Should you encounter problems in this regard, contact [inquiry[at]SitesOnDisplay.com](mailto:inquiry\[at\]SitesOnDisplay.com). Our turnaround time for responding to unsubscribe requests is generally 24 hours.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure 

SitesOnDisplay maintains your email address and other pertinent personal information, provided at the time of your site submission, on the premises. SitesOnDisplay may allow carefully screened vendors the opportunity to send you offers and information that we have deemed may be of value to you. However, these mailings are done by us, not the vendors, and you may opt-in or out of this feature at any time. SitesOnDisplay does not rent or sell email addresses nor any other personal data.

### Cookies

At this time, Cookies are not used on the SitesOnDisplay.com site.

### Security

Your personal information is stored in a protected directory. Access is restricted to SitesOnDisplay staff.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

SitesOnDisplay may amend this policy from time to time. If significant changes are made in the way your personal information is used, we will post a prominent announcement on the site notifying you of the change.

### Questions or Suggestions

Questions or suggestions may be sent to: [Feedback](mailto:inquiry\[at\]SitesOnDisplay.com?subject=RE:Feedback)

To prevent address harvesting, the "@" symbol in the email addresses above have been replaced with [at]. If you wish to contact us, simply copy the appropri ate address into your email client and replace [at] with @.
